Hey there. Welcome to Kansas City.
>> How you doing? How you doing?
>> Congratul Congratulations.
>> Appreciate you. Appreciate you.
>> Okay, here's our local media. Um you'll
see these guys a lot while you when you
get here. Um and they're just going to
ask you some questions and we'll let you
go celebrate.
Okay, we're going to start with Sam
Mcdow with Kansas City Star.
>> Hey, what's up, man? I just uh I got a
couple things for you, but wonder first
just your reaction and maybe your uh
pre-draft communication with the Chiefs.
Does this come as a surprise to you?
>> I mean, obviously, I think it's it's an
obvious case where, you know, um you
know, everybody was saying, you know,
the needs for my position or whatnot,
but to me, like, you know, the the the
communication with the Chiefs wasn't
really like too much to uh so I didn't
really expect it, I would say. Um but
just really my reaction at the time of
getting picked, you know, I all my
emotions came out when I seen that
Kansas City, you know, number come
across my phone. Um you know, it was
just a blessing.
>> And then just I wonder your draft day
experience. I mean, obviously I know
you're at the draft, but who you watched
it with and and who's important to you
in that room?
>> Sure. Um, two of my brothers, two of my
sisters, you know, both my parents,
grandma, grandpa, you know, everybody.
It took a village to get where I'm at.
So, um, you know, everybody just was
enjoying this experience with me.
>> Okay, let's go next to Matt Derek with
Chief's Digest. Go ahead, Matt.
>> Hey, Mansour. Congratulations. And I
hope I got your name correct there. Is
it Mansour? I saw it. Perfect.
>> Excellent. Um, you know, how did you
have you watched much of Trent McDuffy?
Obviously, he was the guy that's you're
kind of gonna be replacing at least on
the roster. Did you watch him play much
and have any thoughts about him as a
player?
>> No, for sure. He's a great player. Um,
you know, I like to study all types of
guys in the league. Um, you know, and he
he's one of the best to do it,
especially with his versatility. So, you
know, just not knowing where I'm going
to fit in, uh, I can fit in anywhere in
that defense bags defense. So, really
just excited to step in and make an
impact. And I know you've played
obviously a lot on the boundary and as
as an outside corner. What's your
comfort level as far as playing inside
the in the slot corner if that's what
the Chiefs ask you to do?
>> Super comfortable. You know, I love
playing inside. I think it's almost even
more fun. You know, you're closer to the
ball, you know, you're in more run fits,
you can bliss more, you know, more
responsibility. So, I think to me the
more responsibility, the funner it is.
Um, so I'm excited.
>> Let's go next to Todd Lebo.
Uh, a couple questions. First off, uh, I
know your head's spinning. Who called
you from the Chiefs? Who did you get to
talk to? Do you And can you kind of let
us go know what you heard on those
conversations?
>> I'm going to be 100% honest. You know,
when they when they called me, I just
started crying. I don't know who was
talking. I was just saying, "Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you." Um,
but then I I talked to I remember I just
talked to Coach Reed. Um, you know, uh,
Mr. V. I just remember those two uh
specifically once I kind of winded down
a little bit, but you know, it was it
was it was know it was a great moment.
>> And tell me about your progression. You
started Virginia Tech, you end up with a
year at LSU. Um did what did you feel
that move to LSU meant for you as far as
getting yourself to this level?
>> No, for sure. It just it gave me the
platform. Um you know, I just wanted I'm
always a guy runs a competition. You
know, I think LSU that was one of the
hardest tasks. I took a a chance. I bet
on myself and it paid off. So, you know,
just playing with great guys,
surrounding myself with the best
competition. Um, I just love that.
>> We'll go next to Jesse Newell.
>> Hey, Mansour. I got a couple for you.
Um, first off, you said that a lot of
tears uh right after you were picked.
Can you take me through the emotions?
What was going through your mind?
>> So, you know, I I get the phone call and
you know, they traded up and I was like,
dang, I wanted to go to the Chiefs, but
you know, I just wasn't expecting it.
Um, so I was like, "Yeah, here it goes."
Then I look down. I'm like, I look
around like for a quick second. Um, and
then I picked up the phone and then I'm
like, "Whoa, like this is crazy." And
then, um, you know, that's when just the
the motion came to me. And, you know, I
was just so blessed to, you know, be on
a team like this.
>> And I think you said on TV they made the
best move in the draft to take you. Can
you explain what you meant by that?
>> It's the best move. Um, you know, I I
truly believe defense wins
championships. Um and you know, let
alone we know with the offense, you
know, you know, we already have now, you
know, the defense, it just makes our job
even even even easier. Um so really just
being able to step in and you see um you
know, the impact, you know, now that the
league is such a passing league and you
know, everybody wants to score points,
so I'm here to shut it down. So I think
that's the best move you can make.
>> Let's go next to Nick Jacobs.
>> And Sydney, I have a followup if I can,
please. Monroe for you. What is it about
football that you love?
>> Man, I I love I love everything about I
love the violence of the sport. Um you
know, and again on a different note, I
love the relationships it brings. You
know, it just bring me around so many
great people um and so many different
bridges more than after football. Um you
know, I just think it's a beautiful game
and I'm just glad to be a part of it.
>> And for you kind of watching a Steve
Spagnolo scheme, what is it that excites
you about being able to play in that
style? Man, I couldn't ask for anything
better, you know, just Spags, you know,
things I hear about him and just, you
know, being on his Zoom call. I did a
Zoom call with him and just the defense
that he has, just the the the
flexibility you could play with and you
could you could play ball and I think
that's what fits me best, you know, just
the way I play ball with anticipation
and, you know, and knowledge, you know,
I think it just fits me great.
>> We'll go next to Steve Walls. Go ahead,
Steve.
Hey, what's up, Mour? Congratulations,
man. appreciate you.
>> Hey, you talked about relationships. Uh
I believe one of your brothers that you
played with at uh at VT, man, Shamari
Connor, he was a senior. You was a
freshman at VT. Uh just talk about being
able to be on the team, you know, again
with him.
>> For sure. You know, when I came um to
Virginia Tech, I was a freshman and
Chamari was, you know, this big old
senior type of dude. Like I I really
looked up to him like, you know, I was
like, "Oh, that's what a college player
is like." Um so just being around
Chamari and just, you know, um that's
one of the best players I've ever played
with. And you know, we talked a little
bit before the draft um that we hope to
get play with each other, but now um you
know, it's just we I got some old
pictures I need to repost, but u you
know, it'll be a blessing.
>> Has he has he called you?
>> No, it's true. I haven't been able to
check my phone. He he text me like he
text me like uh 10 minutes before the
draft, though, and he just said, "Let me
know if you need anything." You know, he
might have known something. I didn't
though, apparently.
>> We'll go next to Vah Gregorian. Go
ahead, Vah.
>> Hey, Mansour. Congratulations. Um,
>> what I what you said this a little bit,
but what did it mean to you that they
drafted up up for you? I mean, does that
come with a little extra sense of
responsibility and excitement? And I'll
have a follow-up, Sid, too.
>> For sure. You know, I think pressure and
privilege, you know, I don't really take
it as if like, you know, I got more
weight on my shoulders or anything, but
it just shows, you know, the how much
they wanted me and you want to be
somewhere your where you're wanted. You
can't ask for anything better than that.
So, um, you know, I'm just glad to be a
part of this program, um, and
organization, and I'm ready to get
started.
>> And a little related to the question
about Chamari, have you gotten to know
Tyron Matthew at all or have have is he
a guy that you've, uh, looked up to and
followed and maybe heard from?
>> Sure. Honeybadger has to be top three
players, you know, in all time,
especially in college football. Um, but,
you know, I just I watch his podcast a
lot, you know, him being me going to LSU
and, you know, him uh being from
Louisiana. Um, you know, I just heard
about, you know, uh, coach Andy Reed's
practices, so I'm already been prepared
for that. Um, and then really just, um,
you know, uh, him supporting me
throughout this process and even when I
commit to LSU, you know, welcome me into
the brotherhood.
>> Okay, perfect. Let's um, we have three
more left. Go ahead, Mark.
>> Hey, Monsur. Welcome here to Kansas
City. Uh, not a lot of top 10 picks get
to immediately play for a team that has
championship aspirations. I'm wondering
how excited are you to get here and play
for the Kansas City Chiefs?
>> N that's what I was saying. I just
really think there's no better
opportunity. You know, a lot of top 10
teams like, you know, they're really not
that not good. Um, but that's not the uh
situation here. You know, we have a
championship team. Um, just had one
little down year, but you know, we're
right back to it. You know, with the
expectations that are here, you know,
I'm expecting to live up to them. So,
I'm ready to go.
Okay, let's go next to Herby. Go ahead,
Herby.
>> Hey, Mansour along with everyone else.
Congratulations and welcome to Kansas
City. You mentioned at the start of this
that you always wanted to play for the
Chiefs. Why did you want to play for the
Chiefs?
>> You said why did I want to play for the
>> Yes.
>> Oh, shoot. Coach Spags. Um, you know,
just the defense and then on top of
that, you know, the whole everything,
the culture, you know, how much the fan
base, the way y'all love the team. Um,
you know, really it's a winning program.
You know, you know who's on the other
side of the ball. Um, so then at the at
the same time, you know, the defense,
just the versatility you get to play
with. They're not going to cornhole you
in one spot. Um, you can you can be a
ball player. So, I think that's the best
situation I can ask for.
>> Okay, last one for you and go ahead
Darren.
>> Hey, thank you. Uh, my welcome to Kansas
City. We we'll welcome you when you get
here, man. I think you're going to enjoy
it very much. Look, you were you were
one of the best players at your position
in college football. How do you feel
like playing at a big-time program,
playing in the swamp, that type of
atmosphere will will allow you to
transfer easily over here to Kansas
City?
>> For sure. I played at Virginia Tech,
too, and that environment is no slouch
either. So, you know, every place I've
been at, you know, it's been crazy
environments and just going to LSU, you
know, the expectations are crazy in the
SEC. You know, it's almost even crazy in
the league, I would say. So just, you
know, coming to the league, um, you
know, really not too much of a
difference for me. You know, I thrive
and I love playing in these, you know,
pressure situations and these pressure
moments. Um, so it's a blessing.
Okay, that's all we have for you and
Kelsey will tell you what's